

Cristian Jiménez Mejía

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Profile

JavaScript (Typescript), React, React Native, Android, iOS and web developer with 7 years of experience designing, developing and maintaining the in house built CRM in Laboratorios Bioline de Colombia, later launched as a standalone company, which is being used by the sales force to register their field activities.

Employment History

Senior software developer, VendorPro, Barranquilla

January 2023 - present

As a standalone enterprise, we created VendorPro as a solution for salesforce management in small companies residing in Colombia, creating a new App with new features all based in React Native and installing a team of 3 developers in which I'm one of the two tech leaders, the app Is now available at Play Store and App Store.

Software developer, Laboratorios Bioline de Colombia, Barranquilla

April 2018 - December 2022

Developed and implemented the CRM that the company is actually using called VendorPro Available at Play Store, which is an important tool used to monitor and save all the sales force activities when they are out in the field, the app can also be used in order to place orders from different clients, register expenses, sales, etc. This app was created using JavaScrip for the web app for administrators and Java for the android app which is used by the sales force, all the data, text, images and audio are stored and managed using Firebase.

Production manager, Laboratorios Bioline de Colombia, Barranquilla

August 2013 - march 2018

I was in charge of the production planning for all the end goods sold by the company, taking into account the sales reports and the forecast for each one of them, I was also in charge of the communication with the sales force in order to prevent future demand changes along the way that may change the forecast drastically

Education

Industrial Engineer, Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

FEBRUARY 2006 - APRIL 2015

Graduated with honors and a 4.21/5 GPA

Msc. Management Engineering, Politecnico di Milano, Como

Details

Barranquilla Colombia (+57) 3005618167 <u>cjimenez0288@gmail.com</u>

Links

Linkedin

Skills

HTML & CSS

Java

JavaScript / Typescript

React / React Native

Excel

Adobe Illustrator

Languages

Spanish

English

Italian

Hobbies

Playing softball Videogames